UI/UX design practitioner with extensive experience in developing digital products and services. Competent with facilitating production workflow between design and code to output pixel-perfect interfaces.

Specialist in responsive web and mobile design, user interface, branding, and graphic design.



geoffreywu.digital



gwu20510@gmail.com



്ര്ര geoffrey-wu



# **Geoffrey Wu**

# **Experience**

### **Crowd Cast UI/UX** Designer

July 2020 - present Tokvo

I worked in a multi-disciplinary environment where I was closely involved with the company at the product, engineering, and marketing/branding levels.

As the sole designer, I took charge on all design-related projects to propel the product and brand image for sustainable growth and stability for the future through the development of a design system.

- » Developed prototype of the app (web and mobile versions) to visualise the end product and prepare for developer handoff; undertook a complete redesign of the web application to address issues with the user experience.
- » Redesigned the product website, reviewing copy and creating graphics to ensure brand consistency, leading to increased unique visitors and improved conversion rates.
- Regularly played an active role in discussions concerning the design of the product and its functionality in regards to providing a smooth user experience.
- Conducted code reviews and communicated with developers regularly to ensure that code implementation matches the design as close as possible.

### **DG Takano UI/UX** Engineer

November 2019 - June 2020 Tokyo

I worked in an agile software development team as the sole UI/UX designer, creating and implementing designs for a Ruby on Rails based web application.

- » Implemented created designs within Rails using HTML (Slim templating), CSS (SCSS & CSS frameworks) and JavaScript (stimulus.js)
- » Experienced with e-commerce site development using Shopify

### **Wisenet Information Systems** Graphic Designer & Front-end Developer

July 2017 - March 2019 Melbourne

I worked with both marketing and development teams to improve the brand's presence and enforce design consistency across visual communications.

- » Created the brand for TupleSMS a low-cost alternative to the main product. I developed the logo, brand guide, website, and marketing collateral.
- Developed a brand style guide for the company to reflect contemporary design trends and ensure conformity across digital and print media.
- » Updated and maintained company websites through WordPress, WooCommerce and Hubspot CMS, allowing for simplified customisation by stakeholders.
- » Produced marketing materials such as business cards, brochures, flyers, and banners for the company to distribute at nationwide conferences.

### Flexe Group **Graphic Design Intern**

May 2017 - July 2017 Melbourne

# **Skills**

#### UI/UX

- » Wireframing & prototyping (Figma, Framer X, Origami)
- » Design system development
- » UX copywriting

### **Development**

- » HTML5 & CSS3 (Sass)
- » JavaScript, AJAX, ES6
- Git, Source Code Management
- React
- Ruby, Ruby on Rails
- » WordPress / CMS development

## Design

- » Adobe Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Dimension)
- » Corporate branding
- » Graphic & print design
- » Motion design & video editing

### **Education**

Le Wagon Fullstack Coding **Bootcamp | Tokyo Campus** 

2019

# **RMIT University | Melbourne**

Bachelor of Design (Digital Media) Graduated with Distinction

2015 - 2017

### OCAD University | Toronto

Student Exchange program

2016

# **Achievements**

- » Pre-advanced level Japanese -JLPT N3 Certification obtained 2018
- » Best Prototype Award Winner -F10 Fintech Hackathon Singapore 2019